882 009 584 📞

patrycja.lulkiewicz@gmail.com

Marcinkowice, Oława (9)

PATRYCJA LULKIEWICZ

WRITER

ABOUT ME

I'm a 5th grade student of Polish Philology at the University of Wrocław. I'm passionate about worldbuilding and writing plots, which can be used in movies, games, TV shows, books... I want to develop my skills, gain experience and share many inspiring ideas with the rest of the team in writer's room. I'm positive, fast-learning, accountable and flexible team player good at problemsolving. I have many interests - most of them are art related.

Skills

Creativity Independence **Teamwork**

English

Polish



Education

2021-present | University of Wrocław Polish Philology Master with teaching specialization.

2018-2021 | University of Wrocław

Polish Philology Bachelor with teaching specialization (Polish and history).

Interests

Literature • History, culture and arts • Education • Sport • Handcraft • Gardening • Games • Makeup • Wellbeing • Music

Experience

2020 - present

Text revisor

Proofreading and editing texts on commission.

2019 - present

Tutor

Individually teaching and guiding kids and adults in Polish, English and mathematics.

Certificates

 "Worldbuilding - how to create an ideal world for a game, film, TV show and book" lead by Adam Flamma.



